

GUVANCH JUMAYEV

Wu He Road 328 Ming Hang Shanghai, China | Tel: +8615773110371 Email address: guvanch.jumayev@hotmail.com;

Summary

Competent Technology Specialist with proficiency in computer networks, web development and technical support.

As a technical support engineer for Microsoft customers and partners I have learnt to deliver value by collaboratively and reactively solving customer problems, providing proactive support advice, contributing to product quality and enhancements and creating self-help assets to broadly reach more customers.

All-around technology with huge limitless desire to learn and improve skills in technology. Good at Web Development HTML, CSS, JS also familiar with technologies such as ReactJS, Node.js, Express and MongoDB (MERN stack).

Experience

Premier Technical Support Engineer Wicresoft - Shanghai, China

Apr 2020 to current time

- Scope a customer issue by collecting the relevant facts and investigate the problem by doing your own research and by involving other teams as needed.
- Consult and collaborate with your immediate peers or colleagues around the world and with management and engineering to resolve service issues.
- Act internally as a customer advocate.
- Empower customers to find information, self-solve when they decide to, and learn more about Microsoft products, services and support.
- Advise customers on how to gain additional value from their Microsoft products.
- Document your technical work and research to help your colleagues, improve the product, and improve the support experience.
- Maintain a proactive approach to customer happiness, identifying customer satisfaction concerns and managing customer expectations.

Education consultant Field education – Putian, China Jun 2019 to Feb 2020

- Researching latest education trends;
- Implementing them in the curriculum;
- Creating interactive (gamified) ways of studying
- Teaching Computer basics, Math in English

PhD student in Central South University

Sep 2018 to Jun 2019

Finished the first year of studies and dropped off the studies at my own will

TM CELL – Ashgabad, Turkmenistan

- -Determining the technology needs of each function;
- Creating an acquisition/purchasing plan and contacting 3rd party provider;
- Technology equipment allocation planning;
- Participating in all professional equipment, communication equipment installation, and deinstallation processes;
- Creating DOT plans;
- Supervision of "Bump In" and "Bump out" processes;
- Monitoring condition of all Technology devices and professional equipment at all venues;
- Dealing with all technology related issues;
- Technical support to organization's employees
- Documenting technology-related incidents
- Train staff on information systems

Education and Training

Master of Science, Computer science and technology Central South University – Changsha, China	2013 - 2016
Chinese Language course Central South University – Changsha, China	2012 - 2013
Bachelor of Science, Information technology State Institute of Transport and Communication – Ashgabad, Turkmenistan	2007 - 2012

Certifications

Cisco Certified Network Associate (CCNA)

Skills

- Office 365 and Exchange Online
- Azure Active Directory
- CISCO Certified Network Associate (CCNA)
- Proficiency in TCP/IP protocols
- HTML, CSS, SASS and JavaScript
- ReactJS, MongoDB, NodeJS, Express
- Technology development
- Online learning
- Research and development

Languages

- Turkmen(Native)
- Russian (Native)
- English IELTS 7.0 (Fluent)
- Chinese HSK-4